merchanttransact.com 2013-11-21

# Merchant Transact : Privacy Policy

Merchant Transact takes its customers’ privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.  

Your Acceptance of These Terms  
By using this Web Site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of Merchant Transact’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Web Site and exit the Web Site immediately. Your continued use of Merchant Transact’s Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.  

What this Privacy Policy Covers  
This Privacy Policy covers Merchant Transact's treatment of information that Merchant Transact collects while you are visiting Merchant Transact’s Web Site, when you utilize Merchant Transact’s hosted applications and when you use Merchant Transact’s services. This policy also covers Merchant Transact's treatment of any information that Merchant Transact's business partners share with Merchant Transact. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Merchant Transact does not own or control, or to people that Merchant Transact does not employ or manage.

Through our service offerings, Merchant Transact acts as a repository for our customers’ data (much like a bank is a cash repository). We realize that the confidential data we house belongs to, and is the sole property of, our customers. As a policy, we will not disclose any customer confidential information, except under the conditions stated in Section 4 of this policy.

Information Collection and Use  
Merchant Transact collects and stores information when you use certain Merchant Transact products or services, or when you visit Merchant Transact pages. Merchant Transact may also receive information from our business partners.

Merchant Transact does not use “cookies” to gather information from its users.

The Merchant Transact collects and stores information required to conduct business transactions requested by our users. By way of example, we collect product pricing and quantity information to process orders. We also collect information required to properly conduct communication between our customers. By way of example, we collect information from purchasers to properly direct business to the supplier(s) identified by the purchaser.

Merchant Transact automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address.

Should you have any questions concerning the data we collect or how it is used, please email your question to [privacy@merchanttransact.com](mailto:privacy@merchanttransact.com)

Information Sharing and Disclosure  
Merchant Transact will not sell or rent confidential information to anyone.

Merchant Transact will only disclose confidential information when:

We have your written consent to share the information;

We need to share your information, as you have directed, to any trading partner to provide the product or service you have requested;

We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Merchant Transact to provide a product or service to you (e.g., Merchant Transact’s Internet service provider, Merchant Transact’s data center service provider). (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);

We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or

When Merchant Transact has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to Merchant Transact users or other persons or violating the Terms and Conditions of use for this Web Site.

ELARIO IS NOT LIABLE FOR THE LOSS OR MISUSE OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES. ELARIO’S LIABILITY RELATES ONLY TO ELARIO’S OWN INTENTIONAL MISUSE OF INFORMATION THAT IS NOT OTHERWISE IN THE PUBLIC DOMAIN.  

Your Ability to Edit and Delete your Account Information and Preferences  
Merchant Transact gives you the ability to edit your Merchant Transact Account Information and preferences at any time.  

Security  
Merchant Transact uses several industry-standard layers of data protection, including IP address validation, SSL-encryption, and password protection to protect data transmissions.  

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Merchant Transact may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.  

Questions and Concerns  
If you have questions or suggestions send an email to [privacy@merchanttransact.com](mailto:privacy@merchanttransact.com)
